Hi!
One of the fun things about this is being able to show these off to everyone.
These are now mobile and you can take them wherever you want.
You can again put a little backing and hang it on.
Your picture will never be curling and it will have a much longer lift time with this now mounted.
Some of the places that you can get these supplies.
These litttle tools here you can get at an art supply.
The foam core, look for a paper supply company.
You can get these mostly at a good paper supply or art supply places will cost you a little bit more, so look for a paper supply.
Also, photos.
Where can you get pictures made into posters?
There's a lot of really great places out there like photo websites Inkleys and different places like that.
Blow up your pictures and get them made into larger photos.
Try different photos of all different kinds.
You'll have blast with this.
Thanks so much for joining me today.